info=Camera works should be improved in technical area.-----comments on THE SIGN<br>The use of music is good, while using voice over to deliver the plot is bad.-----comments on THE SIGN<br>Lighting is problematic especially the night scene.-----comments on THE SIGN
<br><br>
Ending is not delivered well. (comments on SKYWALKER)<br>The title name should be more thoughtful. (comments on SKYWALKER)<br>Camera shots, composition and editing are smoothly executed. (comments on SKYWALKER<br>Director has good control of the kid actor. (comments on SKYWALKER)
<br><br>

Location is very well chosen to enhance the story credibility. (comments on BREATHLESS)
Art direction is very well done. (comments on BREATHLESS)
The opening shot is the most cinematic among all their classmates. (comments on BREATHLESS)
Sound effects is very well done. (comments on BREATHLESS)
Ambience sound and location sound recording are badly treated. (comments on BREATHLESS)
The film has good suspense, and a good pacing. (comments on BREATHLESS)
The ending is well treated and leaves thought to audiences mind. (comments on BREATHLESS)

The characters are not convincing. (comments on BROWN ENVELOPE)
Lack of lighting makes your production quality drop. (comments on BROWN ENVELOPE)
The narrative is problematic. (comments on BROWN ENVELOPE)

Poor casting. (comments on TO BE LOVED)
Not enough preparation on scene design. (comments on TO BE LOVED)
The father character needs more make-up. (comments on TO BE LOVED)

Director has no focus on his work. (comments on THE TRUTH BEHIND)

The lines of the dialogues are cliche, and do not reflect personality of the characters. (comments on NIGHTMARE)
The father has a very stylish but strange impression on the character, which keep distracting audiences from the story. (comments on NIGHTMARE)
The way the director places his camera is unique and thoughtful. (comments on NIGHTMARE)

Sound is treated well and clear, in terms of its SFX, off-screen sound, music, and dialogues. (comments on SUSPECT)
This story is narrated smoothly and patiently.  Very nice drama. (comments on SUSPECT)
In the film, we can see how production designer pays effort in taking care of each props, each character and each circumstances. (comments on SUSPECT)

The idea is very original and executed in a very stylish way. (comments on THE LAST PROMISE)
It's a creative approach to filming. (comments on THE LAST PROMISE)
Dialogues are recorded and mixed very well. (comments on THE LAST PROMISE)
Director lacks consistency in the tone of the movie. (comments on THE LAST PROMISE)