info=Below are some of the comments from the guest speakers and audiences on these student films:<br><br>THE SIGN<br>Camera works should be improved in technical area.<br>The use of music is good, while using voice over to deliver the plot is bad.<br>Lighting is problematic especially the night scene.<br><br>SKYWALKER<BR>Ending is not delivered well.<br>The title name should be more thoughtful.<br>Camera shots, composition and editing are smoothly executed.<br>Director has good control of the kid actor.<br><br>BREATHLESS<br>Location is very well chosen to enhance the story credibility. <br>Art direction is very well done.<Br>The opening shot is the most cinematic among all their classmates.<br>Sound effects is very well done.<br>Ambience sound and location sound recording are badly treated.<br>The film has good suspense, and a good pacing.<br>The ending is well treated and leaves thought to audiences mind.<BR><BR>BROWN ENVELOPE<Br>The characters are not convincing.<br>Lack of lighting makes your production quality drop.<br>The narrative is problematic.<BR><BR>TO BE LOVED<br>Poor casting.<br>Not enough preparation on scene design.<br>The father character needs more make-up.<BR><BR>THE TRUTH BEHIND<br>Director has no focus on his work.<BR><BR>NIGHTMARE<br>The lines of the dialogues are cliche, and do not reflect personality of the characters.<br>The father has a very stylish but strange impression on the character, which keep distracting audiences from the story.<br>The way the director places his camera is unique and thoughtful.<BR><BR>SUSPECT<br>Sound is treated well and clear, in terms of its SFX, off-screen sound, music, and dialogues.<br>This story is narrated smoothly and patiently.  Very nice drama.<br>In the film, we can see how production designer pays effort in taking care of each props, each character and each circumstances.<BR><BR>THE LAST PROMISE<br>The idea is very original and executed in a very stylish way.<br>It's a creative approach to filming.<br>Dialogues are recorded and mixed very well.<br>Director lacks consistency in the tone of the movie.<br><br>