info=As a director and a scriptwriter, I must take this chance to express my inner feelings. I must say thank you and sorry to my group members. I know that I’m NICE (if you know what I mean) when we are working. So thank you all for keeping patience with me. This experience will stay in my memory for the years to come.
(director, DALE)
<BR>
It is not easy to be a camera person, since as I’m a girl, I am not used to hold such a heavy camera on my shoulder for such a long time. It is good for me to learn such experience of filmmaking. I hope our effort can turn into a good viewing experience for the audiences.
(cameragirl, JESS)
<BR>
I give my many ‘first time’ to this group. The first time to be an art director in a short film; the first time for location scouting for the story; the first time to design setting and props for the scene; the first time to design a webpage for the final works for presentation. Be honest, I faced many difficulties along the way but I’m happy that I gain a lot in these 4 months.
(art director, SHIRLEY)
<BR>
I’m so glad that I can accompany those NICE friends to do this project, I did enjoy it very much. The most unforgettable thing is sleeping on the street. The duration of the final outcome is short, but our group did pay much effort on it.
(producer, CRYSTAL)
<BR>
Although there are so much problems along the way, we treasure our time to rehearse as much as we can. After all these, we have built up a very good relationship.
(sound, RACHEL)
<BR>
To be honest, I was bored about this project when we began. But then, I discover the whole process of filmmaking is a problem-solving journey. Although it is hard, this challenge makes us learn how to work with our team members.
(production assistant, SUNNY)
<BR><BR>