info=As a director and a screenwriter, I must take this chance to express my inner feelings. I must say thank you and sorry to my group members. I know that I’m NICE (if you know what I mean) when we were filming. So thank you all for keeping patience with me. This experience will stay in my memory for the years to come.<br>(director, DALE)<br><BR>It is not easy to be a camera person, as I’m a girl, I was not used to hold such a heavy camera on my shoulder for such a long time. It is good for me to learn such experience of filmmaking. I hope our effort can turn into a good viewing experience for the audiences.<br>(cameragirl, JESS)<br><BR>In the production of this story, I have many of my 'first-time's, the first time being an art director in a short film; the first time involved in location scouting; the first time participating in set design and props preparation; the first time to design a webpage for the final works for presentation. Be honest, I faced many difficulties along the way but I’m happy that I gain a lot in these 4 months.<br>(art director, SHIRLEY)<br><BR>I’m so glad that I can accompany those NICE friends to do this project, I did enjoy it very much. Filming at night and staying late in order to make the best out of the production is the most unforgettable thing during the process. Although the running time of the final outcome is short, our group did pay much effort on it.<br>(producer, CRYSTAL)<br><BR>Although there were so much problems along the way, we treasured our time to rehearse as much as we can. After all these, we have built up a very good relationship.<br>(sound, RACHEL)<br><BR>To be honest, I was bored about this project when we began. But then, I discovered the whole process of filmmaking is a problem-solving journey. This challenge makes us learn how to work with our team members.<br>(production assistant, SUNNY)<BR><BR>