info=This is a student group project. It requires students to make a short film (5 - 15 mins.) for the first time, based on an assigned script. The final output would be shown on web platform as well as in screening room. During the process of making the film, students show the ability of handling the pre-production of filmmaking, the hands-on techniques in video production, the multimedia post-production, and the knowledge in web authoring.